https://www.scoutsongs.com/privacy.html

ScoutSongs.com Privacy Statement
This is a web site owned and operated by Chakra Sites, Inc.
ScoutSongs.com can be reached via e-mail at .
Information Gathered:
For each visitor to our Web site, our Web server does not recognize a user's domain or e-mail address. We do collect aggregate information on what pages visitors access or visit. We may collect information volunteered by the visitor, such as survey information, contests and/or site registrations.
The information we collect is used for internal review and is then discarded, used to improve the content of our Web site and not shared with other organizations for commercial purposes.
If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by sending email to us at the above address and telling us that you do not want to receive e-mail from our organization.
Advertisements:
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on ScoutSongs.com.
Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads based on a visitors visit here and to other sites on the Internet.
You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.
Off-Site Links:
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.
Notification of Changes:
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our privacy policy statement page so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
